<resources>
    <string name="app_name">tugas1</string>
    <string name="isi">Worms Zone is a game with a dynamic storyline. Start growing your worm right now. Having tried to get a real anaconda, a small worm never gets stuck in one place – he’s ready to bite everyone. However, there is a danger to be eaten by a more successful player. The Worms are real gourmets. They love trying various gelatinous goodies and everything they meet on their route. There are so many yummies around, that it seems the Worm lives in the arena full of yummy eatings. Therefore, the agile slither Worm grows much faster than in other relative games. So, getting to the leaderboard is possible within the first minutes of playingWorms Zone is a game with a dynamic storyline. Start growing your worm right now. Having tried to get a real anaconda, a small worm never gets stuck in one place – he’s ready to bite everyone. However, there is a danger to be eaten by a more successful player. The Worms are real gourmets. They love trying various gelatinous goodies and everything they meet on their route. There are so many yummies around, that it seems the Worm lives in the arena full of yummy eatings. Therefore, the agile slither Worm grows much faster than in other relative games. So, getting to the leaderboard is possible within the first minutes of playingWorms Zone is a game with a dynamic storyline. Start growing your worm right now. Having tried to get a real anaconda, a small worm never gets stuck in one place – he’s ready to bite everyone. However, there is a danger to be eaten by a more successful player. The Worms are real gourmets. They love trying various gelatinous goodies and everything they meet on their route. There are so many yummies around, that it seems the Worm lives in the arena full of yummy eatings. Therefore, the agile slither Worm grows much faster than in other relative games. So, getting to the leaderboard is possible within the first minutes of playingWorms Zone is a game with a dynamic storyline. Start growing your worm right now. Having tried to get a real anaconda, a small worm never gets stuck in one place – he’s ready to bite everyone. However, there is a danger to be eaten by a more successful player. The Worms are real gourmets. They love trying various gelatinous goodies and everything they meet on their route. There are so many yummies around, that it seems the Worm lives in the arena full of yummy eatings. Therefore, the agile slither Worm grows much faster than in other relative games. So, getting to the leaderboard is possible within the first minutes of playing</string>
    <string name="comment">Comment  :</string>
</resources>
